<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bootstrapping on Service Catalog Tools Workshop</title>
    <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bootstrapping on Service Catalog Tools Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppet account</title>
      <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping/10-puppet-account.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping/10-puppet-account.html</guid>
      <description>Navigate to CloudFormation  Select the AWS CloudFormation service.    Confirm you are in the eu-west-1 (Ireland) region.
 Create a new AWS CloudFormation stack  Select &amp;lsquo;Create Stack&amp;rsquo;    Note that the Factory Initialization Stack has been deployed. If yours has not refer to &amp;lsquo;Install Factory Process&amp;rsquo;
 Select the pre-configured AWS CloudFormation template Service Catalog Puppet can be installed via a pre-created AWS CloudFormation template stored in Amazon S3 under the following URL:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single spokes</title>
      <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping/20-single-spokes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping/20-single-spokes.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? You will need to bootstrap spoke accounts so you can share portfolios with them and provision products into them.
Bootstrapping a spoke account will create an AWS CloudFormation stack in it. This stack will contain the Puppet IAM Role (PuppetRole) which is needed by framework to perform actions in the spoke account.
Using the CLI The following steps should be executed using the Service Catalog Puppet CLI which is an application built using Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groups of spokes</title>
      <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping/30-groups-of-spokes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/installation/30-service-catalog-puppet/20-bootstrapping/30-groups-of-spokes.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? If you have enabled AWS Organizations support you may want to bootstrap all spokes within an organizational unit.
Following these steps will allow you to bootstrap all AWS Accounts that exist within the same organizational unit.
Using the CodeBuild Project In your AWS Account you can find an AWS CodeBuild project named: servicecatalog-puppet-bootstrap-an-ou
  Click Start Build
  Before you select Start Build again, expand the Environment variables override section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>