<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data governance on Service Catalog Tools Workshop</title>
    <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data governance on Service Catalog Tools Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the control</title>
      <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2/100-create-the-control.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2/100-create-the-control.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? We are going to perform the following steps:
 define another product with a version and add it to the existing cloud-engineering-governance portfolio add the source code for our product provision that product into a spoke account  Step by step guide Here are the steps you need to follow to &amp;ldquo;Create the control&amp;rdquo;
Define a product with a version and a portfolio  Navigate to the ServiceCatalogFactory CodeCommit repository again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision the control</title>
      <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2/200-provision-the-control.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2/200-provision-the-control.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? We are going to perform the following steps:
 provision the product aws-config-rds-storage-encrypted  For this workshop, we are using the same account as both the hub and spoke for simplicity; in a multi-account setup, products that are created in a hub account could be provisioned in multiple spoke accounts.
Step by step guide Here are the steps you need to follow to &amp;ldquo;Provision the control&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the product</title>
      <link>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2/300-create-the-product.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-samples.github.io/aws-service-catalog-tools-workshop/40-reinvent2019/150-task-2/300-create-the-product.html</guid>
      <description>What are we going to do? We have provisioned a detective control to look for AWS RDS Instances that have don&amp;rsquo;t have encryption enabled. We can do better, and create an AWS Service Catalog product that meets the encryption requirement by default using service catalog tools. When users create a new RDS instance using this product, encryption at rest is enabled by default and no further configuration is required.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>